designmantic.com 2019-06-05

# Privacy Policy | DesignMantic.com

Right Solution, owner and operator of DesignMantic.com respects the privacy of its customers and the visitors and users to its website. This Privacy Statement informs you of our privacy practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected online and how that information is used. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact DesignMantic.com using the contact information included at the end of this statement.

#### Sites covered by this Privacy Statement

DESIGNMANTIC.COM is a global organization, with legal entities, and multiple websites that cross borders. The DESIGNMANTIC.COM website may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the DESIGNMANTIC.COM website. DESIGNMANTIC.COM does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from DESIGNMANTIC.COM's practices. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites. The personal data you choose to provide to or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by the DESIGNMANTIC.COM Privacy Statement. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information.

#### Collection of personal information

To serve you better and understand your needs and interests, DESIGNMANTIC.COM collects, exports, and uses personal information with adequate notice and consent, along with required filings with data protection authorities, when applicable. For example, when you order products or services, request information, subscribe to marketing or support materials, register yourself on DESIGNMANTIC.COM, create designs and purchase designs or participate in surveys, we will ask you to provide personal information to complete these transactions. The types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include contact information such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address; and other unique information such as user IDs and passwords, billing and transaction information, product and service preferences, contact preferences, educational and employment background, and job interest data.

#### Refer a Friend

If you choose to use a tell-a-friend program on our site, we will ask you for your friend's e-mail address and automatically send your friend a one-time e-mail inviting your friend to visit the site. DESIGNMANTIC.COM uses and stores this information only for the purpose of sending this one-time e-mail and to provide tell-a-friend message blocking, where available.

In addition to the information you provide, DESIGNMANTIC.COM may also collect information during your visit to DESIGNMANTIC.COM website through our Automatic Data Collection Tools, which include Web beacons, cookies, embedded Web links, and other commonly used information-gathering tools. These tools collect certain standard information that your browser sends to our website such as your browser type and language, access times, and the address of the website from which you arrived at an DESIGNMANTIC.COM website. They may also collect information about your Internet Protocol (IP) address, click stream behavior (i.e. the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with DESIGNMANTIC.COM websites) and product information. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web, allowing Web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers use IP addresses to communicate on the Internet, allowing users to browse and shop.

#### How we use your information

The information DESIGNMANTIC.COM collects to understand your needs and interests helps DESIGNMANTIC.COM deliver a consistent and personalized experience. For example, DESIGNMANTIC.COM may use your information to 1\. assist you in completing a transaction or order 2\. communicate with you about products and services 3\. provide service and support 4\. update you on new services and benefits 5\. provide personalized promotional offers 6\. select content to be communicated to you 7\. personalize some DESIGNMANTIC.COM websites 8\. allow you to participate in contests and surveys and 9\. Contact you for market research regarding DESIGNMANTIC.COM products or services. We will give you the opportunity to choose your privacy preferences regarding the communications we send. The testimonials posted on our Web site are only posted with the expressed permission of the individual or company who provided that testimonial. Credit card information is used only for payment processing and fraud prevention. Credit card information and other sensitive personal information required to process a credit decision is not used for any other purpose by our financial services providers or DESIGNMANTIC.COM and will not be kept longer than necessary for providing the services, unless you ask us to retain your credit card information for future purchases.

#### How we share your information

DESIGNMANTIC.COM will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others except as described in this Statement. DESIGNMANTIC.COM shares personal information in the following ways: DESIGNMANTIC.COM retains service providers and suppliers to deliver complete products, services and customer solutions and to assist DESIGNMANTIC.COM with marketing and communication initiatives. These providers and suppliers include, for example, credit card processors, providers of customer support and live-help, email service providers, automated data processors, and shipping agents. Suppliers and service providers are required by contract to keep confidential the information received on behalf of DESIGNMANTIC.COM and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for DESIGNMANTIC.COM. From time to time, DESIGNMANTIC.COM participates in marketing initiatives with other companies. As part of these initiatives, certain DESIGNMANTIC.COM services and marketing communications are delivered at the same time as those from other companies. Some of these services and communications offer you the option to share personal information with both DESIGNMANTIC.COM and the other companies participating in these initiatives. For example, you may receive marketing communications from DESIGNMANTIC.COM and other companies or have the opportunity to register online for software products from multiple companies. If you choose to provide personal information only to DESIGNMANTIC.COM, DESIGNMANTIC.COM will not share this information with the other companies participating in that marketing initiative. If you choose to provide personal information to the other companies, that personal information will be handled according to the privacy policy of those companies.

Except as described in this Statement, DESIGNMANTIC.COM will not share the personal information you provide to DESIGNMANTIC.COM with non-DESIGNMANTIC.COM third parties without your permission, unless to: (i) respond to duly authorized information requests of police and governmental authorities; (ii) comply with any law, regulation, subpoena, or court order; (iii) help prevent fraud or to enforce or protect the rights and properties of DESIGNMANTIC.COM or its subsidiaries; or (iv) protect the personal safety of DESIGNMANTIC.COM employees and third parties on DESIGNMANTIC.COM property. Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, DESIGNMANTIC.COM decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize businesses in some countries. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual purchasers, or the receipt of it from sellers. It is DESIGNMANTIC.COM's practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions.

#### Children's privacy

DESIGNMANTIC.COM does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and does not target its websites to children under 13. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests.

#### Your choices and selecting your privacy preferences

DESIGNMANTIC.COM gives you the choice of receiving a variety of information that complements our products and services. You can subscribe to receive certain product- and service-specific information and also choose to receive DESIGNMANTIC.COM general communications. We give you a choice regarding delivery of DESIGNMANTIC.COM general communications by postal mail, email and telephone. You can make or change your choices about receiving either subscription or general communications at the data collection point or by using other methods, which are listed in the following sections. This option does not apply to communications primarily for the purpose of administering order completion, contracts, support, product safety warnings, driver updates, or other administrative and transactional notices as the primary purpose of these communications is not promotional in nature. The email communications that you receive from DESIGNMANTIC.COM will be provided in accordance with this statement. Some email communications may utilize automatic data collection tools.

#### Communication

Write to the DESIGNMANTIC.COM Privacy office located at the bottom of this email. Be sure to provide your name, email and postal address, and specific relevant information about the DESIGNMANTIC.COM subscriptions that you no longer wish to receive. Please be aware that when you opt out of receiving certain subscription communications, it may affect the services you have chosen to receive from DESIGNMANTIC.COM where accepting the communications is a condition of receiving the services.

#### Access to and accuracy of your information

DESIGNMANTIC.COM strives to keep your personal information accurately recorded. We have implemented technology, management processes and policies to help maintain data accuracy. DESIGNMANTIC.COM provides individuals with reasonable access to personal information that they provided to DESIGNMANTIC.COM and the reasonable ability to review and correct it or ask for anonymization, blockage, or deletion, as applicable. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as requiring a password and user ID, before granting access to your data. To view and change the personal information that you directly provided to DESIGNMANTIC.COM you can return to the Web page where you originally submitted your data and follow the instructions on that Web page, or contact the DESIGNMANTIC.COM Privacy Office.

#### Keeping your personal information secure

DESIGNMANTIC.COM takes seriously the trust you place in us. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, DESIGNMANTIC.COM utilizes appropriate physical, technical and administrative procedures to safeguard the information we collect.

#### Changes to this statement

If we change our privacy statement, we will post the revised statement here, with an updated revision date. If we make significant changes to our statement, we may also notify you by other means, such as sending an email or posting a notice on our home page.

#### Contacting us

We value your opinions. If you have comments or questions about our privacy statement, please send them to the DESIGNMANTIC.COM Privacy Office at the following address:[privacy@designmantic.com](mailto:privacy@designmantic.com)
